[](javascript:void(0))

Legal information
=================

Privacy Statement
-----------------

Cascade Parent Limited trading as Alludo and its subsidiaries (collectively, "**Alludo**", "**us**", or "**we**") are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement describes Alludo’s information practices and the choices available to you regarding Alludo’s use of information that can be used to identify you ("**Personal Data**").

If you are located in the European Union, EEA, UK or Switzerland ("**Europe**"), please see [Section 6](#section-6).

If you are a resident of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, or Virginia, please see [Section 7](#section-7).

If you are a resident of the People’s Republic of China, please see [Section 8](#section-8).

If you are a resident of Japan, please see [Section 9](#section-9).

This Privacy Statement addresses Alludo’s use of information collected through any of our web properties (collectively, the "**Sites**"), our value-added offerings, which include but are not limited to, white paper downloads, seminars, or other similar offerings (collectively, the “**Value-Added Offerings**”) or our software, cloud services or maintenance products (collectively, "**Products**"). We will only collect and use information from you as described in this Privacy Statement. To make a request to Alludo regarding your Personal Data, please place such a request through [this form](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/privacy/form/).

### 1\. The Data We Process and Purposes of Processing

Depending on how you interact with us, we process different kinds of data and in different ways. Some data is automatically processed if you visit our Sites or use our Products. Other data is only processed if you actively submit it to us (like using our web forms to get in touch with us, uploading content to our Sites, registering accounts with us, or sending technical reports to us from the Products you use).

#### Data we process if you visit our Sites:

Even if you are only a visitor on one of our Sites, your computer or device automatically sends technical information to our web servers that we store in log files, including the following "**Website Usage Data**":

* date and time of the visit and the duration of use of the Site;
* the IP address of your device as well as your internet service provider (ISP);
* the broad geographical location of your device: i.e., country, city and (where applicable) state;
* the referral/exit URL;
* the visited subsites of the Site and usage events;
* information about your device (type of device, browser type and version, as well as settings, installed plug-ins, operating system)
* your preferred language

We process Website Usage Data to allow you to surf the Site and to ensure its functionality. We also process Website Usage Data to perform analyses on the performance of the Site, to continuously improve the Site and correct errors, to ensure IT security and operation of our systems, as well as to prevent or uncover abuse. We further process this data in aggregated or pseudonymized form to analyze trends, administer the Sites, track users’ movements around the Site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole or to improve marketing (including serving you personalized, interest-based ads through targeted advertising) as well as the user experience on our Site and guaranteeing the safety of our IT systems. Website Usage Data is processed based on your consent, unless such data is deemed necessary for the functioning of our Sites. We may process your IP address to section/group visitors and test different versions of our Sites based on legitimate interest, i.e. to better understand how our Sites are being used and perceived.

To process Website Usage Data, we use cookies and similar technologies. Click [here](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/cookies/) to review our Cookie Notice. In addition, you are always able to review and update your cookies settings by clicking the “Manage My Cookies” link available at the bottom of our Sites.

#### Data we process if you use our Products:

Alludo processes Personal Data when you install and register one of our Products. Some of this information will be processed automatically when installing our Products. This includes the following "**Product Installation Data**":

* your browser type
* operating system
* device hardware
* other software on your system that interact with our Products
* IP address
* broad geographical location (i.e. country, city and (where applicable) state)
* product version
* hardware or machine ID
* your preferred language
* for CorelDRAW subscriptions only, profile ID
* for cloud service products: Azure AD user information, including User Principal Name and Group IDs, Azure profile information, and name/title of your connecting environment.
* for Parallels Desktop Business and Enterprise Edition to aid administrators in license management: computer name, user name, and activation date.
* for Parallels Desktop Enterprise Edition for virtual machine management: virtual machine names, virtual machine operating system, and last use date.

We request certain "**Product Registration Data**" during registration of our Products, including (items in bold are mandatory):

* your name
* your email address
* postal address, including country
* telephone number
* for certain software products, email address and license or key/serial number (necessary to validate your purchase and activate a product)
* for products that require set up for regional video standards, country or region (necessary because video standards are unique to country/region)
* your business affiliation, including company or organization name, country, city and (where applicable) state, and a business phone number (this data is collected only if you register the business products), if applicable

We use Product Installation Data and Product Registration Data to keep a record of your product license (that is, authenticating and periodically verifying your licensing rights in the product for anti-piracy purposes) and to enable the provision of maintenance or support services to you. We will also use this information to provide in-product messaging with information about products, features, or services offered by Alludo.

We collect information about the way you use our Products after you have installed and registered them, if your in-product settings are set to enable such collection. The specific "**Product Usage Data**" varies depending upon which Product you are using, but may include:

* Product Installation and launch Data
* Product Registration Data (including your name and your email)
* hardware fingerprint
* feature usage
* page clicks
* sign-in information
* type and hardware configuration of your computer or mobile device
* software configuration of your computer, including the list of other software products installed on it which interact with our Products
* for Parallels Desktop only, list of Parallels virtual machines installed on your computer including virtual machine names, and virtual hardware configuration, software configuration of your virtual machines, including operating systems and other software products installed inside your virtual machines and a list of the software products you use inside your virtual machines
* for Parallels Desktop only, software configuration of your virtual machines, including operating systems and other software products installed inside your virtual machines
* for Parallels Desktop only, a list of the software products you use inside your virtual machines for Parallels Desktop as a Service only, end user details (including IP address, operating system/version, browser/version, screen size, device identifier, and application names).
* for Parallels Browser Isolation only, username of end user, time of logon, location and application usage, and general information on websites visited by users.

We process Product Usage Data so that we can facilitate, evaluate, and verify your use of our Products and services. We will also use the Product Usage Data for our own internal statistical and analytical purposes, and to evaluate and enhance users' experience of the Products by identifying customer preferences and analyzing crash data.

In addition, certain of our products may allow you to store, send, receive, edit, sync, share, or otherwise organize or manage files and folders (including any information or data stored in those folders) ("**User Files**"). We will record and store information regarding the size and name of all User Files that you make available via these Products

#### Data we process only if you submit it to us:

When you interact with us on our Sites or using our Products, you can submit Personal Data to us in various situations, including:

**Account Data:** You may need to register an online account with us ("**Your Account**") at one or more of the following sites (or successor sites) depending on the Product you are licensing from us:

If you use a third party service such as Apple, Facebook, or Google (“**Third Party Services**”) to create a new or sign in to an existing account when visiting our Sites or using/registering our Products, we may obtain your personal data like your name and email from that Third Party Service but only when you have consented to that Third Party Service sharing your personal data with us.

If you have registered Your Account with us as a corporate/business user then: (a) we may allow the business who controls the account to access, use, remove, retain and control Your Account and all content uploaded or imported to Your Account; (b) we may provide your personal information to the business who controls the account. As a user of a business account, you may have different agreements with or obligations to the business who controls the account, which may affect Your Account or your content. We are not responsible for any violation by you of such agreements or obligations. If you are a personal user, we will treat Your Account as a personal one meaning that you will maintain sole access and control over all content in Your Account.

**Transaction Data:** In relation to purchases you may make online at our online resellers, such as cleverbridge AG and others, we process your Personal Data that our online reseller shares with us. This information may include:

* billing information, such as your name, email address, billing address, your business affiliation (company or organization name)
* the type of Product you purchase
* the amount you pay in your currency
* subscription ID
* subscription-related URLs (such as purchase confirmation page URL, subscription cancelation URL, invoice PDF URL)

You can view the exact information required in the form provided at point of purchase. We will only use this data to complete your order, for billing purposes, and for internal accounting.

Our sales and finance functions may use your Transactional Data to train our internal AI data models for administrative purposes only.

We do not collect or process the data about your payment instruments such as credit card numbers, banking account numbers or Pay Pal accounts. This information is collected, processed, and stored by our online reseller(s) such as cleverbridge AG and others. Collection and use of financial/payment information is governed by the applicable privacy statement(s) offered by our online reseller(s).

**Technical Report Data:** If you would like to report a technical problem regarding one of our Products, the data you might be required to provide may include:

* product name, version and the license key used for activation (if applicable)
* computer’s hardware ID and configuration
* product configuration files and technical (diagnostic) logs
* computer operating system’s logs
* product crash logs
* any file(s) attached by you to the technical report
* your comment provided for the technical report
* for Parallels Desktop only, snapshots of your computer and virtual machine’s screens
* for Parallels Desktop only, virtual machine name and configuration

**Customer Support Data:** You can communicate with us through the different web-forms and chat functionalities on our Sites. For example, you can use the contact forms to request technical assistance, request information on the status of your order, or otherwise reach out to our customer support team. In order to respond to your request, we will process your IP address and contact data as well as the contents of your request and the uploaded files and/or attachments you have sent to us. Your data related to the request will be deleted when your customer support request is completed or in accordance with statutory or contractual retention periods. Some of our online customer service functionality may include the use of AI to direct service requests and such data to train our internal AI tools.

**Survey Data:** From time to time, we may conduct surveys about our Products. Participation in our surveys is optional. However, if you respond to one of our surveys, you may provide us with Personal Data about you. Unless you otherwise consent, we will only use this Personal Data to determine the types of Products that may be of interest to you and to operate and improve our Product offerings.

**Email/Direct Mail Campaign Data:** From time to time, we may contact our customers directly by mail, email, or telephone to inform about upgrades, new products, promotions, or special offers. However, we will not contact you with any commercial communications that are unrelated to the Products that you have purchased from us unless you have given us your prior explicit consent to receiving such information. When responding to one of these campaigns, you may have the option to provide us with Personal Data, which we will use for the purpose indicated. You can opt-out of receiving future marketing emails from Alludo by clicking on the “unsubscribe” option located at the bottom of the marketing email you wish to opt out of. If you prefer to be removed from all Alludo marketing lists, you can fill out this form or email [privacy@alludo.com](mailto:privacy@alludo.com). Customers cannot opt-out of receiving all transactional emails related to their Alludo account and/or their Product(s).

**Applicant Data:** A copy of our privacy statement for job applicants can be found [here](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/privacy/applicant/).

**Business Contact or Sales Prospect Data:** If you are a business contact or sales prospect that has provided us your Personal Data, we will store your data in our database so that we can follow up on previous business conversations we’ve had with you, provide you additional information about our Products, or assist you in purchasing our Products. We may also share your Personal Data with sales representatives employed with our local affiliates or resellers so that they can work with you to complete any requested purchase of our Products. You can find a list of our resellers [here](https://www.winzip.com/en/partners/locator/).

**Participants in our Value-Added Offerings through third parties:** If you sign-up to an Alludo webinar, download a whitepaper, or participate in our offerings through a third party (eg. our business partners), we may collect or receive Personal Data that you have provided in connection with the offering from such third parties, such as social media platforms, websites, and business partners, or from publicly available sources.

### 2\. Disclosing Personal Data to Third Parties

We treat your Personal Data with care and confidentially and will only pass it on to third parties to the extent described below and not beyond.

We do not sell, rent, or trade Personal Data in the traditional sense (i.e., in exchange for payment). Certain U.S. state privacy laws define the term “sale” broadly to encompass some of our data processing activities, outlined in the “Information for Residents of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, and Virginia” section in this Privacy Statement.

Where our affiliates, resellers, or service providers process Personal Data, they will do so solely on our instructions and have undertaken to comply with strict contractual requirements for the security of your data (including, but not limited to, complying with this Privacy Statement).

**Third Party Services:** If you use a Third Party Service such as Apple, Facebook or Google to create a new or sign in to an existing account when visiting our Sites or using our Products, some of your Personal Data such as IP address of your device, your broad geographical location (country, state (if applicable), and city) and the type of the account you sign up for/login to becomes indirectly known to that Third Party Service.

**Affiliated Companies:** Alludo has affiliates located worldwide, including in the USA, Canada, Belgium, Switzerland, Malta, Estonia, Mauritius, Germany, the UK, Japan, and Taiwan. We share data with our affiliates in the ordinary course of our business for administrative purposes and efficiency. For an overview of our affiliates, as well as their mailing addresses, please refer to [https://www.alludo.com/en/legal/affiliated-companies/](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/affiliated-companies/). All Alludo affiliates have signed the inter-company data transfer agreement incorporating Standard Contractual Clauses of the EU Commission, to ensure protection of your data within the Alludo Group.

**Service Providers:** Alludo transmits data to service providers that enable us to provide our Site and market, sell, and deliver our Products and host our services. This includes the parties providing our third-party cookies and tracking tools, as well as parties providing us with services to assist us in processing transactions, including credit card transactions, handling shipping and processing of orders, providing customer support, managing customer relationships (like Saleforce.com), hosting the Sites (like Amazon Web Services), hosting our Cloud Services (like Azure), performing analysis of our Sites or Products (such as Google or AWS warehouse services). We occasionally also disclose Personal Data to independent auditors acting on our behalf, for anti-piracy or revenue accounting purposes in connection with the internal operations of our business. We sometimes need to disclose your information to these companies in order for them to provide the applicable services.

**Document/File Hosting Providers:** The following information is only collected when using optional features in Alludo’s WinZip software product: For user-initiated file and file link sharing and storage using email, social media, instant messaging and cloud services, login information is requested. For user-initiated file sharing via email, social media, and instant messaging optional contact information can be requested and saved so that it can be accessed for future use by the customer. This data is not shared with third parties for any purpose. This information is only stored locally, on your PC or other computing device.

Some of the Products (like Parallels Desktop and our cloud service offerings) allow you to connect your cloud storage account (such as Azure, Dropbox, Microsoft OneDrive, Google Drive, and Apple iCloud Drive). If you do so, the Product may collect the information about the type of cloud storage you use, as well as information around your organization, such as your organization profile information, your organization name/ID, and the name of your environment. But we neither collect nor share with third parties for any purposes your cloud storage account credentials and your files stored in there.

**Business Transactions:** In the event Alludo goes through a business transaction such as a merger, an acquisition by another company, or a sale of all or a portion of its assets to which this Privacy Statement relates, we may disclose or transfer your information to a third party in connection with or during negotiation of such a transaction.

**Public Authorities:** Although we make every effort to preserve customer privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, such as when we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, litigation, or other legal processes or actions (whether or not initiated by Alludo) to protect Alludo's, our users' or third parties' rights, property or safety. We will transmit data to public authorities such as law enforcement or tax authorities only in the case of a legal obligation to do so based on a request for information from the respective authority.

### 3\. Retention of Personal Data

To the extent permitted by applicable law, we typically retain Personal Data we obtain about you for as long as it is needed (1) for the purposes for which we obtained it, in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Statement, which generally means that we will keep your Personal Data for the duration of our relationship or as long as you keep your account open with us; or (2) to take into account applicable statute of limitation periods and comply with applicable laws, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. You may request that we delete your information or restrict the processing of such information by contacting us as indicated in Section 13 of this Privacy Statement.

### 4\. Reviewing and Requesting Changes to Your Information

**European users: please refer to Section 6 below for your statutory rights**

**California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, or Virginia users: please refer to [Section 7](#section-7)**

Customers may update, delete, access, or change their account information by editing their user, group, or team records. To update your customer billing information, contact our Accounts Receivable department at [accounts.receivable@alludo.com](mailto:accounts.receivable@alludo.com). If you do not have an account, please contact us in accordance with Section 14 below.

If you have signed up to receive marketing emails from Alludo, you can opt-out of receiving future marketing emails by clicking on the “unsubscribe” option located at the bottom of the marketing email you wish to opt out of. If you prefer to be removed from all Alludo marketing lists, you can fill out this [form](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/privacy/form/) or email [privacy@alludo.com](mailto:privacy@alludo.com). Customers cannot opt-out of receiving all transactional emails related to their Alludo account and/or their Product(s).

### 5\. Contact Information of Controller

The data controller is one of the affiliated entities of the Alludo Group as follows:

| **Where Personal Data is Collected** | **Legal Entity** | **Contact Information** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Alludo Sites | Cascade Parent Limited trading as Alludo | Level 6 Duo, 280 Bishopsgate, London EC2M 4RB United Kingdom. Our main establishment in the EU is Corel GmbH, Siemensstraße 30, 63755 Alzenau, Germany |
| Parallels Branded Products and Parallels Sites | Parallels International GmbH | Vordergasse 59 8200 Schaffhausen, CH. Our main establishment in the EU is Corel GmbH, Siemensstraße 30, 63755 Alzenau, Germany |
| Products other than Parallels Branded Products and Corel Sites | Corel Corporation | 333 Preston Street Suite 700 Ottawa, ON K1S 5N4. Our main establishment in the EU is Corel GmbH, Siemensstra |

### 6\. Information for European Residents:

You are not legally required to provide Alludo with the Personal Data described in this Privacy Statement. Further, the contractual relationship that you might have entered into with us by purchasing our Products does not imply any obligation to provide your Personal Data. However, you might not be able to use our Products to the full extent, or in some cases you may not be able to use our Products at all, if you do not provide us with certain data or object to the use of this data.

The [U.S.-based companies of Alludo](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/affiliated-companies/) - Corel Inc., Parallels Inc., and WinZip Computing LLC - commit to the principles outlined in the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce, regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union and European Economic Area member countries, the United Kingdom and Switzerland. We have certified with the Department of Commerce that we adhere to the Data Privacy Framework Principles. 

We sometimes provide Personal Data to third parties to perform services on our behalf. If we transfer Personal Data subject to the Data Privacy Framework to a third party, we will remain liable under the Data Privacy Framework for act or omission of the third party in regards to the Data Privacy Framework unless we can prove we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over the compliance of Corel Inc., Parallels Inc., and WinZip Computing LLC’s with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF) and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF).

To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit [here](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/). If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Statement and the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension of the EU-U.S. DPF, and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF, the Data Privacy Framework Principles shall govern.    

If you believe Alludo processes your Personal Data, you may direct any inquiries or complaints to our team by filling in our [Privacy Intake Form](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/privacy/form/). If you have an unresolved privacy or data use, you may contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at [https://www.jamsadr.com/DPF-Dispute-Resolution](https://www.jamsadr.com/DPF-Dispute-Resolution) If neither Alludo nor our dispute resolution provider resolves your complaint, you may have the possibility to engage in binding arbitration through the Data Privacy Framework Panel. For more information on this option, please see [Annex I](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf) of the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles. 

#### Our Legal Basis for Processing

Alludo primarily processes data as a controller, for the purposes explained above under Sections 1 and 2 of this Privacy Statement. These purposes represent our legitimate interests. At the same time, some of the Personal Data we process is necessary for us to perform a contract with you or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract with you. For example, if you express your interest in purchasing one of our Products, such as by filling out a webform, we will process the Personal Data submitted to comply with your request. This may include sharing your Personal Data with one of our authorized resellers, who will then use your Personal Data to complete the purchase transaction. In addition, we are legally obliged to provide certain information to criminal prosecution or tax authorities in individual cases upon request. In these cases, the legal basis for the processing is either legal requirements or reasons of public interest. Where we process your Personal Data with your explicit consent, this declaration of consent will be the legal basis for processing your Personal Data.

#### Transferring your Data outside Europe

In certain cases, your personal data may be transferred to countries outside of Europe. Alludo ensures that such transfer will be carried out in accordance with the applicable data protection laws. This entails that any party outside of Europe and countries subject to an EU adequacy decision (like Canada and Switzerland) which comes in possession of your personal data must ensure an adequate level of protection, for example by entering into standard contractual clauses.

Please refer to the following for a complete list of [Alludo Sub-Processors](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/sub-processors/) used for Alludo Products.

#### User Profiles

We use your data for "**Profiling**". This means that we use your data to make tailored offers based on your previous behavior as well as to serve you personalized ads. However, we will never process and analyze your Personal Data in the context of Profiling in a way would lead to an automated decision that has a legal effect on you or significantly impairs you in a similar way.

#### Your rights regarding the processing of your Personal Data

As a natural person, you have certain rights as "**Data Subject**". You can assert the following rights:

ACCESS: You have the right to access your Personal Data to know how we are processing your personal data, generally within 1 month of your request;

RECTIFICATION: You can ask us to have inaccurate Personal Data amended;

ERASURE: You can ask us to erase Personal Data in certain circumstances, recognizing that we must always respect data retention legal obligations;

WITHDRAWAL OF CONSENT: You can withdraw at any time any consents to processing that you have given us and prevent further processing if there is no other legitimate ground upon which we can process your Personal Data;

RESTRICTION: You can require certain Personal Data to be marked as restricted for processing in certain circumstances;

PORTABILITY: You can ask us to provide you with a copy of your Personal Data in a such a form that you can send it to a third party;

RAISE A COMPLAINT: You can raise a complaint about our processing with the competent data protection authority in your jurisdiction;

OBJECTION: You have the right to object at any time to the processing of your Personal Data. If you object, we will no longer process your Personal Data in the future unless we can prove compelling grounds for the processing that outweigh your interests, rights, and freedoms or the processing serves to assert, exercise, or defend legal claims.

To exercise your rights regarding Personal Data, or if you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or our privacy practices, please complete this form or contact us at privacy@alludo.com. We strongly encourage you to use the form at the link where possible to ensure the most efficient handling of your submission.

You can assert these rights to us only with respect to the data processing we conduct on our own behalf, as a controller. In the event Alludo acts as a processor of your data for a third party, e.g. your employer, you must refer to the entity acting as controller to assert this right.

Please note that, where you have granted us your consent to process certain Personal Data, you are free to withdraw this declaration of consent with future effect at any point in time.

#### Information about your Right of Objection

1\. Right of objection in individual cases  
In addition to the rights already mentioned, you have the right, for reasons arising from your particular situation, to object at any time to the processing of Personal Data relating to you; this also applies to profiling based on this provision. If you file an objection, we will no longer process your Personal Data unless we can prove compelling grounds for the processing that outweigh your interests, rights, and freedoms or the processing serves to assert, exercise, or defend legal claims. Please also note that, if we terminate the processing due to your objection, the Sites or Products may no longer be available to you or only to a limited extent.

2\. The right to object to the processing of data for advertising purposes  
You also have the right to object at any time to the processing of your Personal Data for the purpose of direct marketing, including any subscription to our newsletters or personalized ads; this also applies to Profiling, insofar as it is associated with such direct marketing. If you object, we will no longer process your Personal Data in the future.

#### Special Categories of Personal Data

Alludo does not process Special Categories of Personal Data.

### 7\. Information for Residents of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, and Virginia (each, a “State”)

Alludo may sell or share Personal Data, as those terms are defined under applicable State privacy laws. Alludo does not knowingly sell or share the Personal Data of consumers under the age of 16.

#### Personal Data Transfers to Third Parties

| **Personal Information Collected** | **3rd parties who may receive the Personal Information (defined in section 2)** | **Categories of 3rd parties to/with whom Personal Information may be sold or shared** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers. | Affiliated companies | Third party cookie and tracking tool providers. Click [here](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/cookies/) to review our Cookie Notice. |
| Vendors |     |
| Commercial information, including products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. | Affiliate Companies | In product messaging and advertisements |
| Vendors |     |
| Internet activity information, including, but not limited to, information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an internet website application, or advertisement. | Affiliate Companies | Marketing services |
| Vendors |     |

#### Sensitive Data

Alludo does not collect Sensitive Personal Data as defined under applicable State privacy laws.

#### Data Retention

We store Personal Data for as long as our contract is in force and as required under applicable law. For more information on how long we retain Personal Data, please refer to section 3.

#### Consumer Rights

Under applicable State laws residents are granted consumer rights that Alludo will uphold:

* Right to know which Personal Data is being collected and access such information
* Right to delete your Personal Data
* Right to correct your Personal Data
* Right to opt out of the sale or sharing of Personal Data. To opt out of sales and shares of Personal Data, click: [Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Data](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/privacy/form/)
* Right to opt out of targeted advertising
* Right to non-discrimination

Any State Customer wishing to exercise a right to access Personal Data held by Alludo can submit a verifiable consumer request to Alludo via Alludo’s [privacy intake form](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/privacy/form/).

You may also submit requests to us via email at [privacy@alludo.com](mailto:privacy@alludo.com).

To verify your identity, we may request that you provide some information about yourself, such as your name, email address, and location. We will only use the data you provide for verification purposes.

#### Appeals – Virginia, Colorado, and Connecticut

Residents of Virginia, Colorado, and Connecticut can appeal denials of their rights requests by emailing us at [privacy@alludo.com](mailto:privacy@alludo.com).

#### Authorized Agents

If you are an authorized agent representing a user from an applicable State, please reach out to us at [privacy@alludo.com](mailto:privacy@alludo.com)

### 8.Information for Residents of the People’s Republic of China

For information pertaining to individuals in the People’s Republic of China please click [here](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/privacy/china/).

### 9\. Information for Residents of Japan

For information pertaining to individuals located in Japan please click [here](https://www.winzip.com/jp/legal/privacy/japan/).

### 10\. Notice for Ad Remover Customers

We do not, through our Ad Remover services, collect any information about the websites you have visited, but collect the aggregate number of ads and trackers you block to improve our ad blocking abilities and speed, and to display estimated amount of time saved from blocking ads. This information does not include any browser history or websites you visit. We retain this information to continuously improve our business, services, and ad blocking intelligence based on aggregating and normalizing the data collected across all systems.

#### Google Limited Use of User Data

The use of information received from Google APIs adheres to the [Chrome Web Store User Data Policy](https://developer.chrome.com/docs/webstore/program-policies/), including the [Limited Use](https://developer.chrome.com/docs/webstore/program-policies/limited-use/) requirements.

#### What information is collected and/or used?

* User Activity - The only user activity we collect is when you interact with the Ad Remover extension and when you visit our website (www.adremover.org). This information is used to improve the overall user experience and provide you the correct information related to Ad Remover
* extension and when you visit our website (www.adremover.org). This information is used to improve the overall user experience and provide you the correct information related to Ad Remover
* Location - We collect your IP address to provide you access to a free trial
* Personally Identifiable Information - If you decide to purchase an Ad Remover subscription after you try it for free, we will collect the following information about you:
    * name
    * email address
    * zip/postal code
    * payment information
* Authentication Information - When you purchase an Ad Remover subscription, we provide you with a license key. This key is used to authenticate your paid subscription.
* All data collected is only used to provide Ad Remover service.

### 11\. Protection of Google user data

Information for WinZip and MindManager users connecting to their Google drive via an API: all operations that are performed between the user’s computer and the Google cloud use the HTTPS protocol and security procedures are in place to protect the confidentiality of the users\` data.

Google Workspace APIs are not used to develop, improve, or train generalized AI and/or machine learning models.

### 12\. YouTube Uploads

Certain video editing Products offer users the ability to upload user videos onto YouTube. To facilitate this, Alludo utilizes YouTube API Services. Use of this feature by users is subject to the YouTube [Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms) and the [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

### 13\. Collecting Information from Children

Alludo’s Sites and Products are not intended for use by children under the age of 18 and we do not intentionally collect any information from users under the age of 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that their child has provided Alludo with Personal Data or that we have otherwise inadvertently collected this information, contact us at [privacy@alludo.com](mailto:privacy@alludo.com), so that we may delete the information from our servers.

### 14\. Changes

Except to the extent limited by applicable law, Alludo reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in the law, our data handling practices, or the features of our business. We will provide notification of changes to this Privacy Statement by prominently posting notice through our Sites. Changes to our Privacy Statement will be effective when posted and the new effective date will be identified.

### 15\. Contact Information

To exercise your rights regarding Personal Data (as described above in this Privacy Statement), or if you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or our privacy practices, please contact us at [privacy@alludo.com](mailto:privacy@alludo.com) or submit a request via our intake [form](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/privacy/form/).

We strongly encourage you to use the form at the link, to ensure the most efficient handling of your submission. Please do not use this form to report technical problems or to raise other issues that are not directly related to data privacy or this Privacy Statement.

Last Updated: September 2024

* © Cascade Parent Limited trading as Alludo. All rights reserved.
  
* [Legal](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/) /
* [Terms of Use](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/terms-of-use/) /
* [Privacy](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/privacy/) /
* [Cookies](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/cookies/) /
* [Do not sell/share my information](https://www.winzip.com/en/legal/privacy/form/) /
* Manage my cookies
